Do you use Shiny?
Oh yes, yes.
We, so, within my organization
are called rPlatform, so
we use everything. We use the Workbench,
the Packet Manager, and the Shiny.
Now the Shiny
has become too popular.
Too popular? 😅
That's why
my team has grown
so much. So we use it
a lot. We have a lot of internal apps
and
yeah, we use it a lot.
There's a lot of internally
facing apps because
when people develop
Shiny apps, there's a skill element
because I always say like, you know, before, let's say
if you're not using Shiny, what was the alternative?
You become a full
dev developer, you learn like HTML,
JavaScript, CSS, and
nobody really knew that. There were like, you know, probably
one or three people within the organization.
But now, because we have the Connect
server, anyone
can spin up a Shiny app
and it's very easy and that's
where we see like a lot of
innovation. And
then when you combine that with
AI, well, that's another level
of capability.
And it's very
easy and
to be honest, it makes it too easy.
I actually have to say no to people
in some cases
because we use it a lot and we have
many, many Shiny apps.
It's too easy
to make a Shiny app. It's like
really great PR and terrible PR
at the same time.